<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Attendance</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">close</string>
    <string name="About">About</string>
    <string name="rollno">Rollno :</string>


    <string-array name="Main">
        <item> Timetable </item>
        <item> Subjects </item>
        <item> Faculty </item>
        <item> Resources </item>
        <item> Calender of events </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Description">
        <item> Gives info about classes and timings alloted for each class. </item>
        <item> Gives Brief syllabus of Every Subject. </item>
        <item> Gives the details about teachers.</item>
        <item> Get all the study materials,extra information. </item>
        <item> Helps to schedule your palns for current semester. </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Week">
        <item> Monday </item>
        <item> Tuesday </item>
        <item> Wednesday </item>
        <item> Thursday </item>
        <item> Friday </item>
        <item> Saturday </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Monday">
        <item>Mobile Adhoc Networks </item>
        <item>Compiler Design</item>
        <item>Tea Break</item>
        <item>Computer Graphics and Visualization</item>
        <item>Management and Entrepreneurship</item>
        <item>Lunch Break</item>
        <item>Batch A1-Computer graphics Lab/Batch A2-WebTechnologies Lab</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Tuesday">
        <item>Unix shell programming</item>
        <item>Web Technologies</item>
        <item>Tea Break</item>
        <item>Management and Entrepreneurship</item>
        <item>Computer Graphics and Visualization</item>
        <item>Lunch Break</item>
        <item>Compiler Design</item>
        <item>Mobile Adhoc Networks </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Wednesday">
        <item>Batch A2-Computer graphics Lab/Batch A3-WebTechnologies Lab</item>
        <item>Web Technologies</item>
        <item>Lunch Break</item>
        <item>Mobile Adhoc Networks</item>
        <item>Management and Entrepreneurship</item>
        <item>Compiler Design</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Thursday">
        <item>Management and Entrepreneurship</item>
        <item>Mobile Adhoc Networks</item>
        <item>Tea Break</item>
        <item>Unix shell programming</item>
        <item>Compiler Design</item>
        <item>Lunch Break</item>
        <item>Web Technologies</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Friday">
        <item>Placement Training</item>
        <item>Tea Break</item>
        <item>Computer Graphics and Visualization</item>
        <item>Unix shell programming</item>
        <item>Lunch Break</item>
        <item>Batch A3-Computer graphics Lab/Batch A1-WebTechnologies Lab</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Saturday">
        <item>No classes Today</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time1">
        <item>9:00AM-9:55AM </item>
        <item>9:55AM-10:50AM</item>
        <item>10:50AM-11:10AM</item>
        <item>11:10AM-12:05PM</item>
        <item>12:05PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>1:00PM-1:45PM</item>
        <item>1:45PM-4:30PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time2">

        <item>9:00AM-9:55AM </item>
        <item>9:55AM-10:50AM</item>
        <item>10:50AM-11:10AM</item>
        <item>11:10AM-12:05PM</item>
        <item>12:05PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>1:00PM-1:45PM</item>
        <item>1:45PM-2:40PM</item>
        <item>2:40PM-3:35PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time3">
        <item>9:OOAM-12:05PM</item>
        <item>12:05PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>1:00PM-1:45PM</item>
        <item>1:45PM-2:40PM</item>
        <item>2:40PM-3:35PM</item>
        <item>3:35PM-4:300M</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time4">
        <item>9:00AM-9:55AM </item>
        <item>9:55AM-10:50AM</item>
        <item>10:50AM-11:10AM</item>
        <item>11:10AM-12:05PM</item>
        <item>12:05PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>1:00PM-1:45PM</item>
        <item>1:45PM-2:40PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time5">
        <item>9:00AM-10:50AM </item>
        <item>10:50AM-11:10AM</item>
        <item>11:10AM-12:05PM</item>
        <item>12:05PM-1:00PM</item>
        <item>1:00PM-1:45PM</item>
        <item>1:45PM-4:30PM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time6">
        <item> </item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Subjects">
        <item>Mobile Adhoc Networks</item>
        <item>Compiler Design</item>
        <item>Management and Entrepreneurship</item>
        <item>Web Technologies</item>
        <item>Unix shell programming</item>
        <item>Computer Graphics and Visualization</item>
        <item>Computer graphics Laboratory</item>
        <item>WebTechnologies Laboratory</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="networks">

        <item>1.Adhoc wireless network :-Introduction,-Cellular and AdHoc Wireless Networks,Applications.Issues in Ad hoc
                wireless networks- Medium access, routing, multi casting,transport layer, pricing, Quality of service, self organization,security, addressing, energy management,
                scalability,deployment. Ad hoc wireless internet.</item>


        <item>2. MAC: MAC Protocols for Ad hoc wireless Networks:-Introduction, Issues in designing a MAC protocol for Ad hoc wireless Networks,
            Design goals of a MAC protocol for Ad hoc wireless Networks, Classification of MAC protocols, Contentionbased protocols(MACAW,MACA-Bl,MARCH).\n\n
            2b) MAC: Contention based protocols with reservation mechanisms(D-PRMA, CATA, RTMAC). Contention-based MAC protocols
            with scheduling mechanism (DPS, DWOP), MAC protocols that use directional antennas.</item>


        <item>3.Routing- Routing protocols for Ad hoc wireless Networks:Introduction, Issues in designing a routing protocol for Ad hocwireless Networks,

            (TCP-F,TCP-BUS,ATCPSPLIT TCP)</item>


        <item>4.Transport Layer: Transport layer protocols for Ad hoc wireless networks: Introduction, Issues in designing a transport layer protocol for Ad hoc wireless Networks,
        Design goals of a transport layer protocol for Ad hoc wireless Networks Classification of transport layer solutions, TCP over Ad hoc wireless Networks
            Classification of routing protocols, Table driven routing protocols (DSDV,WRP,CGSR), On-demand routing protocols (DSR,AODV,TORA) Routing:-Hybrid routing protocol,
            Routing protocols with effective flooding mechanisms, Hierarchical routing protocols, Power aware routing protocols</item>


        <item>5.QoS: Quality of service in Ad hoc wireless Networks:-Introduction, Issues and challenges in providing Qos in Ad hoc wireless Networks, Classification of QoS solutions, MAC
             layer solutions(cluster TDMA), network layer solutions (Ticketbased, TDR, QoS enabled AODV, OQR)</item>


        <item>Text Book:1. C. Siva Ram Murthy and B. S. Manoj, Ad hoc Wireless NetworksArchitectures and Protocols,\nISBN: 978 81 317 0688 6, 2014</item>


        <item>Reference Books1. Stefano Basagni, Marco Conti, Silvia Giordano, and Ivan Stojmenovic,Mobile ad hoc networking ,\nISBN: 978-0-471-65688-3,2010\n\n
            2. C.K. Toh: Adhoc Mobile Wireless Networks- Protocols and Systems,Prentice-Hall PTR,\nISBN:0130078174,2007 \n\n
            3. Jonathan Loo, Jaime Lloret Mauri and Jesús Hamilton Ortiz, Mobile adhoc networks: current status and future trends, Kindle edition,\n
            ISBN 9781439856505-CATW K 12654, 2011</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="compiler_design">
        <item>Introduction: Language Processors, The Structure of a Compiler, The Evolution of Programming Languages, The Science of Building a Compiler, Applications of Compiler
                  Technology, Programming Language Basics.</item>
        <item>Lexical Analysis: The Role Of Lexical Analyzer, Input Buffering,Specifications Of Tokens, Recognition Of Tokens\n\nSyntax Analysis: Introduction, Context Free Grammars.</item>

        <item>Syntax Analysis: Writing a Grammar, Top Down Parsing.Bottom Up Parsing.</item>


        <item>Syntax Analysis: Introduction to LR Parsing, Simple LR Parser, More Powerful LR Parsers, Using Ambiguous Grammars.\n\nSyntax-Directed Translation: Syntax-Directed Definitions
                   Evaluation Order for SDDs, Application of Syntax Directed Translation, Syntax Directed Translation Schemes</item>

        <item> Run-Time Environments: Storage Organization, Storage Allocation of Space, Access to Non Local Data on the Stack,Heap Management, Introduction to Garbage Collection.\n\n
                5b.Code Generation: Issues In The Design Of Code Generator,The Target Language, Addresses in the Target Code, Basic Blocks And Flow Graphs, Next-Use Information, A Simple
                Code Generator.</item>

        <item>Alfred W Aho, Monica S Lam, Ravi Sethi, and Jeffrey D Ullman, "Compilers- Principles, Techniques and Tools"\nPublisher: Pearson Education; Second edition (1 January 2011),
		       \nISBN-10: 8131759024,ISBN-13: 978-8131759028</item>

        <item>REFERENCE BOOKS 1. Andrew W Apple, "Modern Compiler Implementation in C",Cambridge University Press, 1997,\n
		       2. Kenneth C Louden, "Compiler Construction Principles and Practice" Thomson Education, 1997.\n3. Charles N Fischer, Richard leBlanc, Jr, "Crafting a Compiler with C"
               Pearson Education, 1991</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="management">
        <item>Since mobile phones are popular with students and can be used in all walks of life, we have attempted to create an
        </item>

        <item>Although there are many mobile platforms available in the market these days,
		</item>

        <item>Since mobile phones are popular with students and can be used in all walks of life, we have attempted to create an
        </item>


        <item> Androidis an Operating System supporting a large number of applications in smart phones.
        </item>

        <item>One such application that we arediscussing here in the paper is the Academic Scheduler.
        </item>

        <item>the student itself and should have the application installed
		on the smartphone/android device. In our project
		</item>

        <item>The Admin module provide the time tables of Student and teachers from the admin side and the staff and student can access thair time table seperatly.
	     </item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="webtechnologies">
       <item>Fundamentals of Web, XHTML-1: Internet,WWW, Web Browsers and Web Servers, URLs, MIME, HTTP, Security The Web Programmers Toolbox.\nXHTML: Basic syntax
                Standard structure, Basic text markup, Images, Hypertet Links.\nXHTML: Basic syntax, Standard strueture, Basic text
                markup, Images, Hypertext Links</item>

        <item>XHTML -2, CSS: Lists, Tables, Forms, Frames css:Introduction, Levels of style sheets, Style specification formats Selector forms, Property value forms,
      	            Font properties, List properties, Color, Alignment of text, The box model, Background images, The span and devtags, Conflict resolution</item>

        <item>JavaScript: Overview of JavaScript, Object orientation and JavaScript, Syntactic characteristics, Primitives, operations and expressions, Screen output and keyboard input,
		          Control statments, Object crcation and modification, Arrays Functions, Constructors, Pattern matching using regular expressions, Errors in scripts, Examples.</item>

        <item>JavaScript and DHTML Documents: JavaScript and HTML Documents, Dynamic Documents with JavaScript: The Java script execution environment, The Document Object Model
            Element access in JavaScript, Events and event handling,Handling events from the Body elements, Button elements,Text box and Password elements, The DOM 2 event model
            The navigator object, DOM tree traversal and modification.\n\nDynamic Documents with JavaScript: Introductiont to dynamic documents, Positioning elements,Moving clements Element visibility, Changing colors and fonts, Dynamic content,
            Stacking elements, Locating the mouse cursor, Reacting to a mouse click, Slow movement of elements, Dragging and dropping elements\n\n
            XML: Introduction, Syntax, Document structure, Document Type definitions, Namespaces, XML schemas, Displaying raw XML documents, Displaying XML documents with CSS, XSLT
            style sheets, XML processors, Web services.</item>

        <item>PHP: Origins and uses of PHP, Overview of PHP, General syntactic characteristics, Primitives, operations and expressions, Output, Control statements, Arrays, Functions, Pattern matching
                     Form handling, Files, Cookies, Session tracking. Database Access: Relational databases, Architectures for database access, MySQL, Database access with PHP and MySQL</item>

        <item>Text Book: 1. Robert W. Sebesta: Programming the World Wide Web, 4th edition,Pearson education, 2012\nPublisher: Pearson Education; Second edition (I January 2011)\n
                  ISBN-10: 8131759024,ISBN-13: 978-8131759028</item>
        <item>Reference Books:-1. M. Deitel, P.J. Deitel, A. B. Goldberg: Internet and World Wide Web How to H program, 4th Edition, Pearson education, 2011\n
                2. Chris Bates: Web Programming Building Internet Applications,3rd Edition, Wiley India, 2011\n
                3. Joyce Farrell, Xue Bai, Michael Ekedahl: The Web Warrior Guide to Web Programming, First edition, Thomson, 2010.\nWeb Links: http://www.w3schools.com
       </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="unixshellprograming">
        <item> INTRODUCTION: The POSIX Standards, The POSIX.1 FIPs Standard,UNIX Files: File Types, The UNIX anI FieSystem,The UNIX and POSIX File Attributes, Inodes inUNIX System V,
                Application Program Interface to FilesUNIX Kernel Support for Files, Relationship of C Stream Pointers and File Descriptors, Directory Files, Hard and Symbolic Links.</item>
        <item>
            UNIX File APIs: General File APIls, File and Record Locking,Directory File APIs, Device File APIs, FIFO File APIs, Symbolic Link File APls.</item>

        <item>
		    UNIX Processes: The Environment of a UNIX Process:Introduction, main function, Process Termination, Commands Line Arguments, Environment List, Memory Layout of a C
            Program, Shared Libraries, Memory Allocation, Environment Variables, setjmp and longjmp Functions, getrlimit, setrlimit
            Functions, UNIX Kernel Support for Processes.</item>
        <item>Process Control: Introduction, Process Identifiers, fork, vfork, exit, Zombie process,wait, waitpid, wait3, wait4 Functions Race Conditions,
		    exec Functions, Interpreter Files, system Function.</item>
        <item>Process Relationships: Introduction, Terminal Logins, Network Logins, Process Groups, Sessions, Controlling Terminal, Job control, Orphaned Process Groups.\n\n
            Interprocess Communication : Overview of IPC Methods, Pipes, popen, pclose Functions, FIFOs, Message Queues.</item>

        <item>1.Terrence Chan: UNIX System Programming Using  c++,Prentice Hall India,1999.(Chapters 1, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10).\n
            2. W.Richard Stevens: Advanced Programming in the UNIX Environment,2nd edition, Pearson Education, 2005.(Chapters 7, 3, 9, 13, 14, 15).</item>

        <item>1. Marc J. Rochkind: Advanced UNIX Programming, 2nd Edition Education, 2005\n
              2. Maurice J Bach: The Design of the UNIX Operating System Pearson Education, 1987\n
              3. Uresh Vahalia: UNIX Internals: The New Frontiers, Pearson Education,2001</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="computergraphics">
        <item>Introduction: Applications of computer grphics; A graphics system; Images: Physical and synthetic; Imaging Systems The synthetic camera model; The programmers interface;
          Graphics architectures; Programmable Pipelines; Performance Characteristics Graphics Programming: The Sierpinski gasket Programming Two Dimensional Applications.</item>

        <item>The Open GL: The Open GL API; Primitives and attributes; Color; Viewing; Control functions; The Gasket program; Polygons and recursion; The three-dimensional gasket;
	         Plotting Implicit Functions.\n\n 2b.Input and Interaction: Interaction; Input devices; Clients and Servers; Display Lists, Programming Event Driven Input; Menus;Animating Interactive Programs;
	           Design of Interactive Programs,Logic Operations</item>

        <item>Geometric Objects and Transformations: Scalars, Points,and Vectors; 3-D Primitives; Coordinate Systems and Frames Modeling a Colored Cube; Affine Transformations; Rotation,
           Translation and Scaling; Geometric Objects and Transformations; Transformation in Homogeneous Coordinates; Concatenation of Transformations; Open GL  Transformation Matrices.</item>

        <item>Implementation: Basic Implementation Strategies, Four major tasks; Clipping; Line-segment clipping; Polygon clipping Rasterization;Bresenhams algorithm;
	       Hidden-surface removal.\n\n 4b.Viewing: Classical and computer viewing; Viewing with a Computer; Positioning of the camera; Simple projections Projections in OpenGL;
	         Parallel-projection matrices Perspective-projection matrices;</item>

        <item>Lighting and Shading: Light and Matter; Light Sources; The Phong Lighting model; Polygonal Shading; Light sources in OpenGL; Specification of materials in OpenGL</item>

        <item>Text Book:1. Edward Angel: Interactive Computer Graphics A Top-Down Approach with OpenGL, 5th Edition, Pearson Education, 2013.\n1SBN-13: 9788131797259</item>

        <item>Reference Books 1. Donald Hearm, Pauline Baker and Warren Carithers: Computer Graphics with OpenGL, 4th Edition, Pearson Education, 2015.\nISBN-13: 9789332518711\n
	        2. F.S. Hill Ir: Computer Graphics Using OpenGL, 3rd Edition, Pearson education, 2013. ISBN-13: 9780131496705</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cgvlab">
        <item>1a. Program to implement a FLYING KITE\n1b. Create 2D Sierpinski gasket by recursive subdivision of triangle.\n\n
          2a. Write a program to rotate a square. Rotate on mouse left-buttonclicks. On right click, stop rotation\n
          2b. Create 3D Sierpinski gasket by recursive subdivision of tetrahedron.</item>

        <item>3a. Write a program to handle mouse events. Plot points in random colors by pressing the mouse left button. The display window must be cleared when
           you press the mouse right button.\n3b. Write a program to demonstrate the usage of display lists. The list
                  should define various geometric objects like square, rectangle, triangle.</item>

        <item>4a. Write a program to create a font for the letter S of user input thickness\n4b. Write a program to perform rotation of a cube using vertex arrays.\n\n
            5a. Write a program to create a font for the letter O of user input thickness.\n5b. Write a program to draw a color cube and allow the user to move the
             camera suitably to experiment with perspective viewing.</item>

        <item>6a. Write a program to create a chessboard.\n6b. Write a program, using OpenGL functions, to demonstrate propertiesof the light source along with properties of the surfaces of the solid
             object.\n\n7a. Write a program to create a rotating wheel.\n7b. Write a program to draw a square. Use popup menu with options to quit or resize the square. The resize option has submenu with increase
             size and decrease size as options. The increase size must double the size of the square and the decrease size option must reduce the size
             by 2. (half size)</item>

        <item>8a. Write a program to display a hierarchical menu as below using popup menu. When an option is selected, display the option on output window
           View__normal |_print |_web,Edit__cut|_copy |_paste.\n8b. Write a program to create a house like figure and rotate it about a
           given fixed point using OpenGL functions.</item>

        <item>Not mentioned</item>

        <item>Not mentioned</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="wtlab">
        <item>1.Develop and demonstrate a XHTML document that illustrates the use external style sheet, ordered list, table, borders, padding, color, thes (span)and(Divo) tag.\n\n
              2.Develop and demonstrate a XHTML. file that includes JavaScript script for the following problems:\nInput : number n obtained using prompt.Output: The first n Fibonacci numbers\n\n
			  b) Input : A number n obtained using prompt.Output: table of numbers from I to n and their squares using alert.</item>

        <item>3. Develop and demonstrate a XHTML file that includes JavaScript script that uses functions for the following problems:\na) Parameter: A string.Output: The position in the string of the left-most vowel\n
               b) Parameter: A number.Output: The number with its digits in the reverse order.\n\n
               4. a) Develop and demonstrate, using JavaScript script, a XHTML document that collects the USN ( the valid format is: A digit from 1 to 4 followed by two upper-case characters followed by
               two digits followed by two upper-case characters followed by three digits; no embedded spaces allowed) of the user. Event
               handler must be included for the form element that collects this information to validate the input. Messages in the alert windows
                must be produced when errors are detected.\nb) Modify the above program to get the current semester also (restricted to be a number from 1 to 8)</item>

        <item>5. a) Develop and demonstrate, using JavaScript script, a XHTML document that contains three short paragraphs of text, stacked on top of each other, with only enough of each showing so that the mouse
                 cursor can be placed over some part of them. When the cursor is placed over the exposed part of any paragraph, it should rise to the top
                  to become completely visible.\nb) Modify the above document so that when a paragraph is moved from
                  the top stacking position, it returns to its original position rather than to the bottom.\n\n
               6. Develop and demonstrate, using JavaScript script, a XHTML document which that collects the Password (the valid format is: 7 to 16 characters
                  contain only characters, numeric digits, underscore and first character must be a letter, no embedded space is allowed) of the user. Event handler must be included for the form element that collects this
                  information to validate the input. Messages in the alert windows must be produced when errors are detected.</item>

        <item>7. a) Design an XML document to store information about a student in Dr.AIT. The information must include USN, Name, Branch, Year of
                  Joining, and e-mail id. Make up sample data for 5 students. Create a CSS style sheet and use it to display the document</item>

        <item>8 a) Write a PHP program to store current date-time in a COOKIE and the web page upon display the Last visited on date-time on reopening of the same page.\n
              8 b.Write a PHP program to store page views count in SESSION, to on web page increment the count on each refresh, and to show the count  on the webpage.\n\n
            9. Create a XHTML form with Name, Address Line I, Address Line 2, and E-mail text fields. On submitting, store the values in MySQL table.
            Retrieve and display the data based on Name. (using php).</item>

        <item>Not mentioned</item>

        <item>Not mentioned</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>Unit-1</item>
        <item>Unit-2</item>
        <item>Unit-3</item>
        <item>Unit-4</item>
        <item>Unit-5</item>
        <item>TEXT BOOK</item>
        <item>Reference books</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="Faculty">

        <item>Harish.G</item>
        <item>Praveena.M.V</item>
        <item>Harishkumar.H.C</item>
        <item>Vinodkumar.K.P</item>
        <item>Madhu.B</item>
        <item>Shylaja.K.R</item>


    </string-array>


    <string-array name="harishg">
        <item>Name :Harish.G\nDesignation :Asst.Prof.\nQualification :M.Tech\nRoom_No :xyz</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="praveen">
        <item>Name :Praveena.M.V\nDesignation :Programmer\nQualification :M.Tech\nRoom_No :xyz</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="harishkumar">
        <item>Name :Harishkumar.H.C\nDesignation :Asst.Prof.\nQualification :M.Tech\nRoom_No :xyz</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="vinodkumar">
        <item>Name :Vinodkumar.K.P\nDesignation :Asst.Prof.\nQualification :M.Tech\nRoom_No :xyz</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="madhu">
        <item>Name :Madhu.B\nDesignation :Asst.Prof.\nQualification :M.Tech\nRoom_No :xyz</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="shylaja">
        <item>Name :Shylaja.K.R\nDesignation :Asso.Prof.\nQualification :M.Tech\nRoom_No :xyz</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="fnames">
        <item>faculty Details\n</item>


    </string-array>



    <string name="resources">\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020\u0020Click the below link to get notes and  related stuff....</string>

    <string name="linktodownload">
        <a href="https://tinyurl.com/cse-a-section-notes">\nCLICK HERE TO DOWNLOAD</a>
    </string>
</resources>
